# TIM BIN

+ (885) 975248187

tim.bin@student@passerellesnumeriques.com

Web Developer a Web Developer is responsible for programming code that tells websites how to operate. Web Developers the specialize in either "front-end" ("client-side") development or "back-end" ("server-side") development. Strong professionals do both, and we're called "Full-Stack Developers.



## **Experience**

01/2021 to 12/2021

#### **Web Development**

PN Cambodia, Phnom Penh

- Motivate and coach myself to tasks, studying, and repair goals.
- Create and modify my self-schedules with grade levels in mind.
- Better coding there are HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Python.
- Joining with program other at school like make game, writing code, Challenge with classmate.
- Maintain detailed logs about assignment, lesson.

12/2021 to 03/2022

#### **Web Development**

PN Cambodia, Phnom Penh

- Working with Graphic, User Experience, or Web Designers to help ensure design ideas can be made into a website that is easy to user.
- Structuring a website so that it is easy to find through a search engine (this is part of Search Engine Optimization or SEO).
- Developing websites that work and look good on any screen, from 24-inch computer monitors to five-inch smartphone screens (this is called responsive design)
- Troubleshooting, fixing bugs, and glitches.
- Building in functionality and responsivity

# **Highlights**

- Effective coding
- Teamwork capacity
- Operability and commitment
- Ability to motivate people around and maintain good relations.
- Resistance to stress
- Good manners

### **Education**

Soft-Skill **Professional life** and Hard-Skill **Information Technology:** 2021-2022 PNC college, NGO

### **Hobbies**

- Playing guitar great way to unwind, destress, and keep the mind sharp.
- Reading Book on weekends
- Cooking for family at home.